Matthew A. Grisham

227 Olive Street, Leavenworth, KS 66048 913-333-67-98 magrishams@gmail.com

Career Summary

5 years working as a Correctional Officer at Correction Corporation of America with 1 year of experience. I worked at Armed Forces Bank in the customer service area for 2 years effectively resolving disputes between the bank and our clients.

Confident

Determined

Knowledgeable

Calm under

Candid

Discrete

pressure

Courageous

Perceptive

Analytical

Career History

Unemployed, School.

I was injured on the job in 2019 and had to rehabilitate my back and went back to school as I could no longer physically work in a correctional workplace. 2019-2022

Correctional Officer

Correction Corporation of America, Leavenworth, KS 66048

2014-2019

- Monitor inmate activities, restrain disorderly inmates and manage disciplinary action
- Promote the cleanliness of the facility and inspect prison cells for contraband
- Emergency Response Team

Teller

Armed Forces Bank Call Center, Leavenworth, KS 66048

2012-2014

- Listen to customers' questions and concerns and solve problems following the bank's procedures.
- Authorize to cancel bank cards that have been stolen and issue new cards
- If a certain problem is particularly difficult, or if the customer is being unreasonable, you must know when to pass the call on to a manager

Librarian

Ike Skelton Combined Arms Library, Fort Leavenworth, KS 66048

2010-2011

- Help clients find, reserve and check out library resources
- Keep the library tidy and re-shelf books

Education

Graduate, Lansing High School, Lansing, Kansas Attending Kansas City Community College, Leavenworth, Kansas